Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 7. Campaign Files, 1976-2004 TJU.2010.01.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 2004 Senatorial Campaign, 1980-2004; VIII.
  - General Election, 1980-2004; 2.
    - Arlen Specter, Allentown accomplishments, 2003 (Box 1253, Folder 31)
    - Arlen Specter, Campaign budget, 2004 (Box 1253, Folder 32)
    - Arlen Specter, Campaign kickoff, 2004 (Box 1253, Folder 33)
    - Arlen Specter, Flyers, 2004 (Box 1253, Folder 34)
    - Arlen Specter, Miscellaneous votes, 1991-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 35)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Abortion, 1995-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 36)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Agriculture and dairy, 1980-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 37)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Business, 1983-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 38)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Civil rights, 1988-2002 (Box 1253, Folder 39)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Congress, 1981-2003 (Box 1253, Folder 40)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Defense, foreign policy and security, 1981-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 41)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Education, 1996-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 42)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Energy, 1981-2003 (Box 1253, Folder 43)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Environment, 1994-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 44)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Gun rights, 1983-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 45)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Healthcare, 1991-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 46)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Immigration, 1990-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 47)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Judicial issues, 2002-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 48)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Legal issues, 1992-2003 (Box 1253, Folder 49)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Party votes, 1985-2002 (Box 1253, Folder 50)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Religion, 2004 (Box 1253, Folder 51)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Social issues, 1996-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 52)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Social Security, 1981-2003 (Box 1253, Folder 53)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Steel, 2003 (Box 1253, Folder 54)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Taxes and spending, 1981-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 55)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Trade, 1982-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 56)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Transportation, 1995-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 57)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Veterans, 1984-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 58)
    - Arlen Specter, Opinion, Welfare, 1981-1999 (Box 1253, Folder 59)
    - Arlen Specter, Talking points, 2002 (Box 1253, Folder 60)
    - Arlen Specter, Toomey statement, 2003 (Box 1253, Folder 61)
    - Arlen Specter, Voter analysis, 1980-2002 (Box 1253, Folder 62)
    - Support for Specter, 2000-2004 (Box 1253, Folder 63)
    - Survey on Pennsylvania, 2004 (Box 1253, Folder 64)
    - Patrick Toomey, Voting record, 1981-2002 (Box 1253, Folder 65)
    - Voting studies, 1981-2003 (Box 1253, Folder 66)
    - General campaign files, 2004 (Box 1260)
    - General campaign files, 2004 (Box 1261)
    - General campaign files, 2004 (Box 1262)